export const data = [
  {
    question: "What is Java?",
    option1: "A) A type of coffee",
    option2: "B) A programming language",
    option3: "C) An operating system",
    option4: "D) A mobile phone brand",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is a variable in Java?",
    option1: "A) A reserved word",
    option2: "B) A container for storing data",
    option3: "C) A type of loop",
    option4: "D) A special character",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following data types is not primitive in Java?",
    option1: "A) int",
    option2: "B) double",
    option3: "C) String",
    option4: "D) char",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the output of the following code snippet?\nint x = 10;\nSystem.out.println(x > 5 ? 'Greater than 5' : 'Less than or equal to 5');",
    option1: "A) Greater than 5",
    option2: "B) Less than or equal to 5",
    option3: "C) 10",
    option4: "D) Error",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the result of 5 + 8 * 3 in Java?",
    option1: "A) 39",
    option2: "B) 24",
    option3: "C) 29",
    option4: "D) 31",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following statements is used to terminate a loop in Java?",
    option1: "A) stop",
    option2: "B) end",
    option3: "C) break",
    option4: "D) terminate",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the keyword used to define a class in Java?",
    option1: "A) class",
    option2: "B) void",
    option3: "C) define",
    option4: "D) new",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'System.out.println()' method in Java?",
    option1: "A) To read user input",
    option2: "B) To display output on the console",
    option3: "C) To perform mathematical operations",
    option4: "D) To declare variables",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following loops is used when the number of iterations is known?",
    option1: "A) for loop",
    option2: "B) while loop",
    option3: "C) do-while loop",
    option4: "D) if-else loop",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the syntax for declaring an array in Java?",
    option1: "A) int array = new int[];",
    option2: "B) int[] array = new int();",
    option3: "C) int[] array = new int[] {};",
    option4: "D) int[] array = new int[5];",
    ans: 4,
  },
];
